Yor's other identity
約兒的另一個身分
is Thorn Princess.
是睡美人
Your mission this time is to protect.
妳這次的任務是擔任護衛
In order to protect a VIP mafia member seeking asylum,
為了保護黑手黨重要成員逃亡至海外
a plan was set for Yor to board a luxury cruise. Meanwhile...
約兒被安排登上豪華郵輪 與此同時...
You won the grand prize!
抽中最大獎啦!
...Anya won the grand prize at a raffle,
安妮亞在抽獎活動中抽中了首獎
so the entire Forger family ended up on the same cruise ship.
結果佛傑家所有人 都登上了同一艘郵輪
There were many assassins secretly on board the ship.
船上潛入了大量殺手
Sickle-and-Chain Barnaby!
鎖鏈手巴納比!
What should I do? We'll cause a commotion!
怎麼辦?再這樣下去會造成騷動的!
Wow! You're so cool, Circus Lady!
馬戲團姐姐好帥喔!
You're a lifesaver, Anya!
做得漂亮,安妮亞!
Anya works hard to keep Yor's other identity a secret from Loid.
安妮亞很努力在洛伊德面前 幫約兒隱瞞另一個身分
Heroic Anya!
勇者安妮亞!
I can barely calm my heart from this exciting adventure!
因為這場刺激的冒險 內心好興奮,平靜不下來!
So damn uncool.
難看死了
Yor repeatedly dodges the assassin's attacks.
約兒多次躲過殺手的攻擊
For what am I...
我究竟是為了什麼才...
I found you!
找到人了!
During the fireworks show,
在煙火秀期間
the deadly battle between Yor and the assassins ensues.
約兒與眾多殺手們展開殊死戰
I just wanted to protect his carefree life.
我只是想守護那個孩子 讓他無憂無慮地生活
I'll continue doing that. In fact, even more so now.
我會繼續做下去,不對 現在更需要繼續做下去
I'm sure Loid will give me his approval. He will understand.
洛伊德先生一定會認同我的 他會諒解我的
I will not stop fighting!
我絕不會...停止戰鬥!
ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
(遠藤達哉原創作品 連載於集英社《SHONEN JUMP PLUS》)
MISSION:34 THE HAND THAT CONNECTS TO THE FUTURE
劇名:任務:34 維繫未來的手
The fireworks were beautiful!
煙火好漂亮喔!
I'm glad you liked it. But sorry,
妳喜歡就好,只是很抱歉
I couldn't find Yor.
沒找到約兒小姐
This ship is too big.
這艘船實在太大了
Oh no!
慘啦!
I had completely forgotten about Mother!
完全把母親忘個一乾二淨!
I have to find her right away!
必須趕快找到她才行!
The State Security Service seems to be in a frenzy. What's happening?
保安局人員看起來很慌張 發生什麼事了嗎?
Urgent... crew... Planted in a room...
緊急...人員...房間裡有...
Bom... A bomb at the bottom of the ship?
炸...船底有炸彈?
What did he just say?
他剛剛說什麼?
Who planted it? And for what reason?
是誰裝的?出於什麼目的?
What should I do? Should I gather some intel? No.
怎麼辦?該去蒐集情報嗎?不對
I'm sure the State Security Service will handle it.
保安局會想辦法處理的
It'll be risky for me to meddle.
貿然插手太危險了
But I also have to think of the worst-case scenario.
但是我得想好最糟情況的對策
To prevent a greater risk, I'll have to make some sacrifices.
要避免更大的風險的話 就不得不做出犧牲
But I can't leave Anya behind. What should I do?
但我也不能丟下安妮亞不管 怎麼辦好呢?
Father.
父親
Anya's not done having fun.
安妮亞還沒玩夠
Hey...
喂...
Darn, at a time like this...
偏偏在這種時候...
I'm going to play over there, so you go back to your room.
我要去那邊玩,父親自己回房間吧
Oh, it's a childcare center. This is convenient.
是托兒中心,也太剛好了
Fine. I'll pick you up in a little while, so stay here until then.
知道了,那我晚點再來接妳 乖乖在這裡等我喔
Okay.
好
Please take good care of my daughter.
我女兒就拜託了
Her name is Anya.
她叫做安妮亞
I'll take good care of her.
明白了
Yay! I can play with balls!
耶,可以玩球了!
All right. Let's get down to business.
很好,現在去辦正事
All right, Anya. What would you like to play with?
好,安妮亞,妳想玩什麼呢?
I'm playing with a ball.
安妮亞在玩球
Yes, you are! You're so amazing!
說得對,妳好棒喔!
I'm going to get tired of this soon.
這個我很快就會玩膩了
I'm tired of it.
我玩膩了
Yes, you sure are.
說得對,那是當然的
I want to draw.
安妮亞想要畫畫
Sure. Hold on.
當然好,等我一下喔
All right, what should we draw?
好,我們要畫什麼呢?
Wait... Anya...
奇怪...安妮亞呢?
Well? Can you defuse it?
怎麼樣?有辦法拆除嗎?
Shut up. I'm trying to concentrate.
安靜啦,我正努力集中精神
We're counting on you. There are tons of VIPs on this ship.
就靠你了,船上有不少重要人物呢
That's why you need to shut up.
都叫你安靜了
I heard there was a bomb around here.
我聽說這附近有炸彈
Yes, it's over here.
對,在這邊
Excuse me. I used to work in the bomb disposal unit
打擾了,我以前在海軍待過
in the marines. Perhaps I can be of help.
爆裂物處置小組,或許我能幫得上忙
Yes!
太好了!
Is it possible to transport this bomb somewhere else?
有可能將炸彈移送到別的地方嗎?
Impossible.
不可能
It's rigged with a trap.
上面設有陷阱
It's a B-CP62 model time bomb.
B-CP62型的計時炸彈
It's the model commonly used by Western extremists.
是西方激進派常用的型號
Could the target be an Eastern VIP?
犯人的目標難道是東國重要人物嗎?
Or maybe this entire ship.
還是針對整艘船呢?不對
No, I haven't received any intel about such activities.
我沒收到有關這類活動的情報
It could also be a setup disguised as a Western operation.
也可能是故意偽裝成是西國所為
Hey, how is it? Do you think you can handle it?
喂,怎麼樣?有辦法處理嗎?
No problem at all.
沒問題
I'll have Father take care of the bomb. I have to go help Mother. Where is she?
炸彈交給父親解決 安妮亞要去幫母親,她在哪裡?
She killed all the well-known assassins. What a scary woman.
那些有名的殺手竟然都被幹掉了 真是恐怖的女人
That's the voice of a bad guy!
是壞人的聲音!
It's time to make an exit.
是時候閃人了
I made enough money here.
錢已經賺夠了
I'll get out of here before the hyenas come after me.
趁那些鬣狗還沒追來,趕緊走人了
You guys can continue fighting there until your time runs out.
你們就在那邊打打殺殺直到爆炸吧
It's coming from the front of the ship.
是從船的前面傳來的
This ship will soon sink to the bottom of the ocean.
這艘船很快就會沉入海底了
No one will know what's happening until they're dying.
沒人會知道自己怎麼死的
I lost the bad guy!
跟丟壞人了!
Never mind that! I need to find Mother right now!
不管了,要趕緊找到母親!
She's at the roof towards the front of the ship!
船前面的屋頂...
That's Mother's stabbing tool!
那是母親拿來刺人的東西!
Not close enough!
還差一點!
I can't get close enough to finish him off!
距離不夠近,無法殺掉他!
Mother is right above me! She's struggling because she has no weapon!
母親就在上面! 沒有武器,所以打得很辛苦!
She's too far. I can't hear her.
太遠了,我聽不到了
How can I climb up? Where are the stairs? There are none!
墊腳的東西...什麼都沒有!
Anya will save Mother!
安妮亞一定會救母親!
Let this reach her!
看我的...
Rising hope!
希望之箭,發射!
Hey, don't make any sound!
喂,別發出聲音!
It's not me! What the hell was that sound right now?
不是我,剛剛那是什麼聲音?
Once that monster of a woman finds us, we'll be finished.
要是被那怪物般的女人發現 我們就完蛋了
I know that. Now's our chance, while she's fighting that sword guy.
我也知道 趁她跟拿刀的對打,只有趁現在了
We'll use this opportunity to kill our target, Gretcher!
要把握這個機會,幹掉目標葛瑞切!
We won't be stuck here forever, right?
我們應該不會關在這裡一輩子吧?
We'll kill them and get out of here right away! Let's go!
幹掉他們之後就馬上離開,上吧!
Just as planned.
如我所料
Did I hear gunshots?
後面好像有槍聲?
That's my...
那是我的...
Hey, I'll end this with one last stroke.
來吧,我用下一擊了結妳
What a fool. She's charging straight at me.
真蠢,竟然直接朝我這邊衝
That old man.
臭老頭
What happened to Mother's battle?
母親的戰鬥怎麼樣了?
It's finally over. I'm so tired.
終於結束了,真的好累
Mother won! All thanks to Anya!
母親贏了!一切多虧有安妮亞!
I have to let Olka and her family out.
得把奧爾嘉夫人他們放出來才行
The bomb has been defused!
炸彈解除了!
- Great work! - It was nothing.
- 幹得好! - 沒什麼
Being surrounded by State Security is more nerve-wracking than the bomb.
相較於炸彈 被保安局的人包圍更讓我緊張
What is it?
怎麼了?
Goodbye, Princess Lorelei.
永別了,蘿樂萊公主號
Let me hear the agony as you sink to death.
讓我好好聆聽妳沉入黃泉的哀號吧
I wonder how my weapon ended up in a place like that.
可是我的武器 究竟為什麼會掉在那種地方呢?
Was there someone else...?
難道有別人...
Oh crap. I need to leave.
糟了,我得走了
I guess the wind carried it over here.
應該是風吹過來的吧
Director, are you all right?
部長先生,您沒事吧?
There are still more bombs?
還有其他炸彈?
If the purpose of this bomb was to sink the ship,
如果設置炸彈的目的是要把船炸沉
the amount of explosive powder here isn't enough.
這樣的炸藥量還不夠
We should have the passengers evacuate.
果然還是要讓船上乘客去避難
Evacuate where? We don't know the location or number of the possible bombs.
去哪裡避難? 炸彈的數量跟位置通通都不清楚
Plus, all the passengers are VIPs. We can't cause a commotion.
而且所有乘客都是大人物 我們不能引起騷動
So the State Security Service needs to save face.
保安局的面子問題嗎?
You better not make this public!
你知道這千萬不能說出去吧!
Order all available agents to search the ship, and the crew.
要所有有空的人 都去船上搜索,船員也去
Make sure the VIPs don't find out what's happening.
務必確保所有大人物 不會察覺到發生什麼事
I have to hurry and return or the lady at the Kid's Room will get mad at me.
得快點趕回去 不然遊戲室的姐姐會罵我的
Dammit... it hurts. I need to remove the bullet.
該死!好痛,必須取出子彈才行
Straightforward attack won't work. I need to come up with a new plan.
正面進攻沒用,必須重新構思新計畫
I'll kill her for sure.
我一定要殺了她!
It's... it's the bad guy!
是...是壞蛋!
What's with this kid?
這小鬼是怎樣?
This smell... Is it explosives?
這個氣味...是炸藥嗎?
There's a bomb inside the clock?
時鐘裡有炸彈?
There are lots more in addition to the one Father is looking for.
除了父親在找的炸彈 還有很多其他的炸彈
Don't tell me... that bastard set this up...
難道說是那個混蛋做的...
Dammit.
可惡
This is an emergency! I have to let Father know!
大事不妙了,必須讓父親知道才行!
But I don't know where Father is!
可是現在換成父親不知道在哪裡!
And I can't tell him anyway, because he'll find out about my secret.
而且也不能告訴他 不然他就會發現我的秘密了
Oh, this is not good. There are bombs on board this ship!
事態嚴重,這艘船上竟然有炸彈!
They told me to search the lower deck thoroughly, but where do I start?
上頭交代我搜遍下層甲板 可是要從何找起啊?
Excuse me.
不好意思
How can I help you, young lady?
有什麼我可以幫妳的嗎,小妹妹?
I just saw a strange man fooling around,
我剛剛看到有個怪叔叔到處晃
sticking boogers on that clock.
還把鼻屎黏在那邊的時鐘上
It's dirty, so please clean it up.
很髒耶,請你打掃乾淨
Boogers?
鼻屎?
I'm sorry, young lady, but I'm really busy right now.
抱歉啊,小妹妹 但是叔叔現在真的很忙
A report of a suspicious man at a time like this...
不,這種時候 收到有可疑人士的情報...
It's probably nothing, but it won't hurt to check.
雖然應該沒什麼問題 但還是去看看好了
Okay, I'll go take a look.
知道了,我去看一下好了
Like I said...
所以說啊...
Those fireworks were amazing....
剛剛的煙火真精彩...
Please excuse me...
客人,打擾一下...
Tomorrow, on the island...
明天在島上...
I still have good reception.
這邊的收訊仍然很棒
Please take it easy, Director!
請不要逞強啊,部長先生!
It seems like all the assassins up there got killed.
看來上面的殺手全死光了
Hey there, eavesdropper.
嗨,偷聽鬼
Where are you planning to go by yourself?
打算一個人去哪裡啊?
You were still alive?
你竟然還活著?
You're the one who planted the bombs, huh?
炸彈是你放的吧?
You were planning to blow all of us up?
打算把所有人都炸飛嗎?
You were defeated. Stop making a fuss.
喪家犬少在那裡大聲嚷嚷
This is a chance to have the target and Garden sink to the bottom of the ocean.
這可是讓目標 還有花園葬身海底的大好機會
Did you forget that our client's friends are also on this ship?
你難道忘了 我們委託人的客戶也在船上?
They're not worth worrying over.
反正他們也無足輕重
Rest assured. The bombs were set, disguised as a Western operation.
放心吧,我把炸彈偽裝成西國所為
If all goes well,
一切順利的話
this will start a war, and weapons will sell like crazy.
就能引發戰爭 軍火生意勢必會很興隆
It'll make our client very happy.
這樣我們的客戶也會很滿意
Whatever. Start up the boat. We have a new plan.
算了,開船吧,我們有新計畫了
Who said you could come on board?
誰說要讓你搭船了?
There's only enough water and supplies on this boat for one person.
船上的食物跟飲水只有一人份
Then I'll put those supplies to good use.
這樣的話,那就都是我的了
Bombs were found in Cargo Compartment Three,
第三貨物艙、壓載水艙上層
the upper part of the ballast tank, and the boiler room.
還有鍋爐房都發現了炸彈
Yes. Okay.
是,好
If it's that type of bomb, it was most likely set by the same bomber.
如果是那種構造的話 極有可能是同一人所為
Defuse it, whilst being careful with the trap I mentioned.
那就麻煩你們拆除了 記得小心我提過的陷阱
All right, let's move on.
很好,下一個
What? Another one on the upper floor, at Deck Eight?
什麼?上層第八甲板也有嗎?
Here it is.
在這裡
It was placed in such a crowded area? Sinking this ship isn't their goal?
在這種人來人往的地方? 所以他們的目的並非把船炸沉?
We're going to be repairing the clock.
我們要修理一下時鐘喔
We'll clear this area first.
必須先撤離人群...
No, this bomb is about to explode. What should I do?
不行,這顆炸彈所剩的時間不多了 該怎麼辦?
It's simple maintenance.
只是單純維修
Hey!
你幹嘛!
- I'll go throw this into the sea! - What?
- 我要直接丟到海裡! - 什麼?
I'll let you in on a secret before you die.
在你死之前,就告訴你一個祕密吧
The second fireworks show will be starting soon.
第二場煙火秀很快就會開始了
You'll be able to hear the symphony of screaming and crying
等一下就可以從藏在整艘船的竊聽器
coming from the bugs hidden all around the ship.
聽到人們哭喊尖叫交織而成的交響樂
Wait! That clock is... an antique!
等等,那個時鐘是... 古董啊!
That was close. Wait, did I see something there?
真是好險 剛剛下面好像有什麼東西?
What was that sound just now?
剛才那個聲音是什麼?
Is it another firework?
又是煙火秀嗎?
Make some announcement over the intercom to prevent panic.
麻煩廣播一下 胡謅點什麼,以免引起騷動
Yes, sir.
瞭解
All right! He got rid of the bomb! All thanks to Anya!
太好了,爆炸危機解除! 都是安妮亞的功勞!
I found you!
找到妳了!
You're not supposed to leave on your own!
妳怎麼可以自己跑掉!
M... Miss... I'm sorry but I really needed to poop...
大...大姐姐...對不起 我剛剛急著大號才...
Then you should've told me that! Let's go back.
那也應該先跟我說一聲啊,回去了
Wait! There might be another explosion!
等等,可能還有炸彈啊
What? You need to poop again?
什麼?妳還沒大完嗎?
Come on, let's go to the bathroom.
走,去上廁所
Do a thorough check of every section of this ship including the upper deck.
船上每一區 包括上層甲板都要再仔細檢查過
There's a chance terrorists are still on board.
有可能恐怖份子還在船上
Please ask the State Security Service agents to be on guard round the clock.
麻煩保安局人員 24小時全天候保持警戒
Yes, sir!
是!
I heard an explosion a while ago.
我剛剛聽到了爆炸聲
There may still be assassins on board. Don't let your guard down.
船上可能還有殺手,不要掉以輕心了
The preparation is done. It's a little early, but let's lower the boat.
好,一切準備就緒 雖然早了點,先把船放下去吧
Stay under this blanket until you're far away from the cruise ship.
在遠離郵輪前 請先用這條毛毯遮掩一下
I understand.
知道了
I wish you well!
希望你們到了那邊一切安好!
Thank you so much.
真的非常謝謝妳
Oh... your clothes will get dirty with blood...
那個,您的衣服會髒掉的,有血...
He wants to give you a farewell hug.
孩子也想給妳一個道別的擁抱
No... my hands are dirty and sticky...
不用啦,我的手又髒又黏的...
Those hands
就是這雙手
have connected him with his future.
維繫了這個孩子的未來呀
He's so warm.
真的...好溫暖
Maybe it's something impossible for you.
也許這對妳而言不可能
Maybe it's none of my business. But...
也許是我多管閒事,不過...
I pray that you and your family
我希望妳跟妳的家人
can enjoy a peaceful life.
能夠過上安穩祥和的生活
There seems to be no problem.
看來沒問題了
We'll just wait for confirmation that the other boat has picked them up.
接下來只要等接應船那邊聯繫就好
Don't let your guard down until morning...
天亮之前都不要放鬆警戒...
Don't become sentimental.
不要自己在那邊感傷了
You mustn't forget that we're just common soldiers.
別忘了,我們不過是一介士兵而已
I'm sorry!
對...對不起!
By the way, I forgot to relay the message that came in for you.
對了,我忘了轉達妳一件事
Forger is requesting to meet up with you at tomorrow's port of call.
佛傑希望明天 可以在停靠的島上跟妳碰面
Loid and Anya made that request? But...
洛伊德先生他們嗎?可是...
I'll keep watch for any remaining assassins.
提防殘黨的工作就交給我吧
Go with your family. It's your reward for completing your mission.
跟妳家人去玩吧 這是妳完成任務的獎勵
Ice your wound to prevent your face from swelling.
臉上的傷不想被發現的話 記得冰敷才不會腫起來
Try to hide the wound on your chest too.
還有胸口的傷可別露出來
Yes, I will hide it! I won't be wearing any swimsuits!
不...不會發生那種事! 我又不會穿泳裝
I think we're safe for now.
現在應該已經安全了
I'm sure I can leave the rest to the State Security Service.
剩下的交給保安局應該就沒問題了
Sorry, I'm late.
抱歉,我來晚了
She fell asleep while she was waiting for you.
她等你等到睡著了
Sorry.
真是不好意思
It was an emergency situation,
雖說剛剛是緊急狀況
but I once again ended up leaving my family behind.
但我又再次把家人拋諸腦後了
What are you saying, Twilight?
你在說什麼啊,黃昏?
This "family" is also part of my mission.
“家人”也是我的任務之一啊
No, this time, the mission was to take a vacation, which isn't really a mission...
不對,這次的任務是度假 所以也不算是任務...
MISSION:35 PART A: ENJOY THE RESORT TO THE FULLEST
(任務:35 A Part:享受度假勝地吧)
PART B: BRAGGING ABOUT VACATION
(B Part:炫耀休假)
Subtitle translation by: Lili Morita
字幕翻譯:洪貞韻